<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   <title>pgDay Paris</title>
   <description>News for the annual Parisian PostgreSQL conference</description>
   <link>http://www.pgday.paris/</link>
   <author>org@pgday.paris (pgDay Paris)</author>
   <atom:link href="http://www.pgday.paris/rss/blog.rss"
     rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

   <item>
     <title>Announcing pgDay Paris 2017</title>
     <author>org@pgday.paris (pgDay Paris)</author>
     <link>http://2017.pgday.paris/blog#announcing-pgday-paris-2017</link>
     <guid>http://2017.pgday.paris/blog#announcing-pgday-paris-2017</guid>
     <pubDate>Wed, 1 Feb 2017 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
     <description>
         <![CDATA[
    <p><a href="/2017/">pgDay Paris
        2017</a> is the third annual one-day, one-track PostgreSQL conference,
    held in Paris, France. This year's conference is planned for <time
        datetime="2017-03-23">March 23rd, 2017</time>.</p>

    <p>This year, all presentations are in English in order to bring to Paris
    the very best of the international community and to show how PostgreSQL is
    used around the globe.</p>

    <p>Here is what you'll see at pgDay Paris 2017:</p>
    <ul>
        <li><p><strong>A PostgreSQL DBAs Toolbelt for 2017</strong></p>
            <p><em>Kaarel Moppel</em>, a consultant from Austrian PostgreSQL
            company Cybertec, takes us on a tour of handy tools and scripts
            that every DBA should know about.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>Corruption War Stories</strong></p>
            <p><em>Christophe Pettus</em>, CEO of American company PostgreSQL
            Experts, shares with us his experiences with data corruption and
            how he was able to overcome it.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>Can't imagine what a newbie can do with PostgreSQL on
                Linux in a month</strong></p>
            <p><em>Sylvie Aune</em>, from SA InfoConsulting, shows us how easy
            getting up to speed with PostgreSQL can be. A must-see for
            newbies!</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>Measuring and Reducing PostgreSQL Transaction Latency</strong></p>
            <p><em>Fabien Coehlo</em>, a professor at L'École des Mines de
            Paris, walks us through transaction latency causes and
            solutions.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>A look at the Elephants trunk - PostgreSQL 10</strong></p>
            <p><em>Magnus Hagander</em>, member of the PostgreSQL Core Team,
            code committer, and president of PostgreSQL Europe, highlights all
            the new features of the upcoming version 10.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>Infrastructure Monitoring with Postgres</strong></p>
            <p><em>Steven Simpson</em>, a software engineer at StackHPC,
            questions the need for &quot;specialized&quot; databases and
            demonstrates that a single PostgreSQL instance is capable of
            handling large amounts of data.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>MLS PostgreSQL - Implementing Multi-level Security in
                PostgreSQL with RLS and SELinux</strong></p>
            <p><em>Joe Conway</em>, VP of PostgreSQL Engineering at American
            company Crunchy Data Solutions and code committer, breaks down how
            to properly secure your PostgreSQL installation from top to
            bottom.</p></li>
        <li><p><strong>Replication &amp; Recovery in PostgreSQL 10.0</strong></p>
            <p><em>Simon Riggs</em>, CTO of international company 2ndQuadrant
            and code committer, unveils the much anticipated new logical
            replication.</p></li>
    </ul>

    <p>As always, the hallway track is where you get to meet and talk to both
    PostgreSQL experts and users!</p>

    <p>See full descriptions of both the presentations and the speakers <a
        href="/2017/schedule/">here</a>,
    and don't forget to <em><a
        href="/2017/registration/">register</a></em>!</p>

    <p>For all the latest news and information, <a
        href="https:/www.twitter.com/pgDayParis">follow us on Twitter</a>.</p>
         ]]>
     </description>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>

